const qBank = [
    {
        question:
          "Which pet is objectively better?",
        answers: ["Cat", "Dog"],
        correct: "Cat",
        questionId: "101"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which color is the best?",
        answers: ["Green", "Blue", "Purple", "Red"],
        correct: "Green",
        questionId: "102"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which genre is better?",
        answers: ["Fantasy", "Sci-Fi"],
        correct: "Fantasy",
        questionId: "103"
      },
      {
        question:
          "How do you sleep?",
        answers: ["Back", "Front", "Side"],
        correct: "Side",
        questionId: "104"
      },
      {
        question:
          "What's the best flavor of icecream?",
        answers: ["Chocolate", "Vanilla", "Strawberry"],
        correct: "Vanilla",
        questionId: "105"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you want to hire Daniel",
        answers: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct: "Yes",
        questionId: "106"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which style of cuisine is better",
        answers: ["Mexican", "Chinese", "Greek"],
        correct: "Greek",
        questionId: "107"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Morning person or evening person?",
        answers: ["Morning", "Evening"],
        correct: "Morning",
        questionId: "108"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Big picture or detail oriented?",
        answers: ["Big Picture", "Detail Oriented"],
        correct: "Big Picture",
        questionId: "109"
      },
      {
        question:
          "Javascript or Python",
        answers: ["JavaScript", "Python", "IDK"],
        correct: "JavaScript",
        questionId: "110"
      },

]

export default qBank;